Guide to the Christian Conference of Asia Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Program Areas / Activities, Series IV
  - Mission and Evangelism
    - Correspondence and Staff Records
      - Lourdino A. Yuzon, 1978 June- 1987 September
        - Correspondence re. 1985 CCA General Assembly, 1985-1985 (Box 18, Folder 5)
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Godwin R. Singh, 1987 October - 1992 November
        - Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 18, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Dhyanchand Carr, 1993 March - 1998 June
        - Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 18, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 11)
        - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 12)
        - Correspondence re. Unemployed Young People Association., 1994 (Box 18, Folder 13)
        - Correspondence re. Church of South India, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Daniel S. Thiagaraiah, 1993 January - 2000 November
        - Correspondence re. Consultation on Journeying Together with Indigenous Peoples in Their Search for Life., 2002 (Box 18, Folder 15)
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 18, Folder 16)
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 18, Folder 17)
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Programme
      - Early Programme
        - Interchurch Aid for Mission and Service. Correspondence, 1967-1974 (Box 18, Folder 19)
        - Interchurch Aid for Mission and Service. Annual report, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 20)
        - Asian Missionary Support Fund. First draft for comments, report of operation., 1965-1969 (Box 18, Folder 21)
        - Let My People Go, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Asian Missionary Support Programme (AMSP)
        - Correspondence re. Funds and Accounts
          - AMSP, 1974-1975 July (Box 18, Folder 23)
          - AMSP, 1974-1979 (Box 18, Folder 24)
          - AMSP, 1975 August -1979 July (Box 18, Folder 25)
          - AMSP, 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 26)
          - AMSP, 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 27)
          - AMSP, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 28)
          - AMSP, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 29)
          - AMSP, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 30)
          - AMSP, 1980-1983 (Box 19, Folder 1)
          - AMSP, 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 2)
          - AMSP, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
          - AMSP, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 4)
          - Correspondence re. applications, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
          - Correspondence re. applications. Korea, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
          - Correspondence with Maran Yaw re. application, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 7)
          - Correspondence with Prasanna Kumari re. application, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 8)
          - Correspondence with Sumiyo Yamaguchi and Tatsuu Fukui re. application, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 9)
          - Studies prepared for a consultation of the Asian Missionary Support Fund, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
          - Directory of AMSP- supported personnel, 1976-1980 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Inter-Religious Dialogue
        - Correspondence
          - Inter- Religious Dialogue, 1976-1983 (Box 19, Folder 12)
          - Inter- Religious Dialogue, 1977-1982 (Box 19, Folder 13)
          - Inter- Religious Dialogue, 1979-1983 (Box 19, Folder 14)
          - Inter- Religious Dialogue, 1979-1983 (Box 19, Folder 15)
        - Papers and consultations
          - Report of the Secretary on Inter-Faith Dialogue, 1970 (Box 107, Folder 2)
          - Sibu consultation preparatory study materials, 1970 (Box 107, Folder 3)
          - Muslim-Christian Reconciliation Study Special Committee, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 4)
          - Hong Kong consultation on Muslim-Christian Dialogue, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 5)
          - "Proclaiming the Gospel in Animistic Cultures" by D. G. McKenzie, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 6)
          - Report on Inter-Religious Youth Workcamp in Indonesia, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 7)
          - Second National Muslim-Christian Dialogue in the Philippines, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 8)
          - "Christian-Muslim Dialogue in Relation to Basic Communities in Asia" by W.M. F. Hofsteede, OFM, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 9)
          - "Political Aspects of Islamic Resurgence in the World with Special Focus on Asia" by T. B. Simatupang, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, Reports
      - Minutes
        - Minutes of the meeting of Programme Committee on the Mission and Evangelism, 17-23 Feb.1986., Hua Hin, Thailand (Box 19, Folder 16)
        - Minutes of Programme Committee on Mission and Evangelism, 21-23 January 1983, Singapore (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - Reports
        - 1986 programmes and events (Box 19, Folder 17)
        - Programme and budget, 1986,1987 (Box 19, Folder 18)
        - Report on programme events, 1986 October - 1987 January (Box 19, Folder 19)
        - Budget, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 20)
        - Monthly reports, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 21)
        - Programme and travel plans, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 22)
        - Updates, newsletter, 1994-1995 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Conferences, Consultations, Workshops
      - Missionary consultation on the Church 's Mission to the Nations in this Ecumenical Era, Malaysia, 28-30 April, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Preparatory planning for a consultation among conservative evangelicals, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Orientation Programme for Asian Missionaries, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - Consultation on Missionary Service in Asia Today, Kuala Lumper, Malaysia, 23 Feb., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Consultation on Missionary Service in Asia Today, Kuala Lumper, Malaysia, 23 Feb. List of participants., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - Consultation- Seminar on Ecumenical Sharing of personnel and Funds, Manila, Philippines., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Working Group on Moratorium,Singapore,12-13 Dec., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Inter- Religious Organization, Dialogue between Muslims and Christian in Singapore, 1974,1975 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - Consultation on Evangelism, Singapore, 29 Nov.-5 Dec.1979 (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - Consultation on Evangelism, Singapore, 29 Nov.-5 Dec.1979 (Box 19, Folder 32)
      - "The challenge of Islam from Asian Churches", Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, 5-10 Feb.1980 (Box 19, Folder 33)
      - Consultation on Equipping Local Churches for Mission Commission on Evangelism and Mission, Manila, Philippines, 5-13 Dec.1981 (Box 19, Folder 34)
      - Consultation on Equipping Local Churches for Mission Commission on Evangelism and Mission, Manila, Philippines, 5-13 Dec.1981. A case study paper by Jose Gamboa, Jr. (Box 19, Folder 35)
      - Sharing of Experience in Evangelism, North Sumatra, Indonesia, 25-29 Nov.1982 (Box 19, Folder 36)
      - Workshop in evangelism in Context, North Sumatra, Indonesia, 25-28 Nov.1982 (Box 19, Folder 37)
      - Workshop in evangelism in Context, North Sumatra, Indonesia, 25-28 Nov.1982 (Box 19, Folder 38)
      - FABC-CCA Joint Consultation on Inter- Faith Dialogue, Singapore, 5-11 July.1987 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Asia Mission Conference, Seoul, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 19)
      - Theological roundtable on " Frontier in Christian Mission", Hong Kong, 11-17 Nov.1999 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Theological roundtable on " Frontier in Christian Mission", Hong Kong, 11-17 Nov.1999 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Regional consultation on Mission and dialogue, Colombo, Sri Lanka, 23-29 Feb.2000 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Regional consultation on Mission and dialogue, Colombo, Sri Lanka, 23-29 Feb.2000 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Regional consultation on Mission and dialogue, Colombo, Sri Lanka, 23-29 Feb.2000 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Ecumenical Enables ' Programme( Reading the Bible with New Eyes), Bangkok, Thailand, 28 Mar.-2 Apr.2001 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Related Organizations
      - Frontier Internship in Mission (FIM)
        - Correspondence re. Zukifly Lubis's application, 1977-1979 (Box 20, Folder 8)
        - Minutes of the International Committee, Geneva,1-4 Oct.1982 (Box 20, Folder 9)
        - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1983 January- May (Box 20, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1983 June-August (Box 20, Folder 11)
        - FIM Correspondence re. coordinator, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Collected Materials
      - Allahabad Agriculture Institute :principle report to the Alumni and friends., 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Papers and write ups, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Papers and write ups, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Papers and write ups, 1980-1984 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Papers and write ups, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Papers and write ups, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Papers and write ups, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Papers and write ups, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Workshop on the Case Study Method and Case Writing, Singapore, 22-26 Feb.1982 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous papers including "The Hong Kong Consultation and Before: a Backgrounder" by Feliciano V. Carino and "The Woman's Question and the Male Christology" by unknown author, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Past, Present and possibility Future Missionary Situation in Hong Kong: A description and interpretation, undated (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Theological Concerns
    - Administrative Records
      - Correspondence with the Association of Theological in South East Asia, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, includes Theological Concerns circular letters, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence re. Faith and Commission, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Planning for the First Ecumenical Asian Theology Conference, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Meeting minutes from the Programme Committee on Theology Concerns, 1978-1983 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Meeting minutes from the Programme Committee on Theology Concerns, 1983 January 17-19 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Monthly reports, 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Second Ecumenical Asia Theological Conference papers, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Additional Programme Committee minutes and reports, 1983-1989 (Box 100, Folder 28)
    - Conferences, Consultations, and Workshops
      - CCA Sponsored
        - Dialogue with Other Faiths and Its Implication for Discerning God's Mission, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 15)
        - CCA HKCC Consultation on the Theological Implication of 1977, 1992 April 28-30 (Box 26, Folder 16)
        - Colloquium on Methods of Doing Theology with and Ecumenical Perspective, 1993-1996 (Box 26, Folder 17)
        - Asia Conference on Church and Society, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 18)
        - Additional consultations, 1994-1996 (Box 107, Folder 13)
      - Other Conferences
        - The International Ecumenical Congress on Theology, 1980 February 20-March 2 (Box 26, Folder 19)
        - Programme for Theology Cultures in Asia's Theological Seminar Workshop V: Doing Theology with People's Symbols Images, 1988 May 29-June12 (Box 26, Folder 20)
        - Programme for Theology Cultures in Asia's Theological Seminar Workshop V: Doing Theology with People's Symbols Images, 1988 May 29-June 12 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Collected Materials
      - Association of Theological Schools in South East Asia (ATSSEA) meeting minutes, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - ATSSEA Joint Regional Planning Commission for Theological Education, 1975 March 17-2? (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - ATSSEA circulars, letters, and meeting minutes, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - ATSSEA circulars and meeting minutes, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - ATSSEA meeting minutes, 1976 October 4-9 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - ATSSEA Consultation on Christian Ministry in Asia, 1977 March (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - ATSSEA Triennial meeting, 1977 March 22-26 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Asian Theology papers by Carlos H. Abesamis and Masao Takenaka, 1962-1974 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Asian Theology papers by Carlos H. Abesamis and Masao Takenaka, 1966-1973 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Asian Theological papers, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Asian Theological papers, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Asian Theological papers, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - International Association for Mission Studies meeting minutes and program materials, 1978-1985 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Papers on interreligious dialogue between Islam and Christianity, 1978-1984 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous papers and essays, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Urban Rural Mission
    This series documents the work of Urban Rural Mission, which became part of Faith, Mission, and Unity upon CCA restructuring in 2000. It is predominately composed of administrative files and staff records, correspondence, collected material, country files, and conference and consultation materials. Administrative files include partner agency correspondence and reports, Urban Rural Mission secretary correspondence, financial reports and statements. Country files contain correspondence collected material, country profiles. This series also contains URM-funded project reports and funding proposals. Conferences and consultation topics include globalization, industry, labor, and social justice. This sub-series contains conference papers, meeting minutes, participant invitations and correspondence, programs, as well as general planning materials.
    - Administrative records
      - Correspondence
        - ACISCA, 1974-1976 (Box 146, Folder 1)
        - Amity Foundation, 1991-1994 (Box 146, Folder 2)
        - Asia Pacific Student Association, 1990-1993 (Box 146, Folder 3)
        - Asia Pacific Mission for Migrant Filipinos (APMMF), 1991 (Box 146, Folder 4)
        - Asian Committee on Community Organization (ACCO), 1971-19792 (Box 146, Folder 5)
        - Asian Committee for People's Organization (ACPO), 1972-1975 (Box 146, Folder 6)
        - Asian Committee for People's Organization (ACPO), 1989-1995 (Box 146, Folder 7)
        - Asian Committee for People's Organization (ACPO) training, 1985-1988 (Box 159, Folder 16)
        - Asian Centre for the Progress of People (ACPP), 1991-1994 (Box 146, Folder 8)
        - Asian Cultural Forum on Development (ACFOD), 1973-1975 (Box 146, Folder 9)
        - Asian Indigenous Peoples Pact (AIPP), 1991-1994 (Box 146, Folder 10)
        - Asian Migrant Center, 1992-1993 (Box 146, Folder 11)
        - Asian Regional Exchange for New Alternatives (ARENA), 1981-1995 (Box 146, Folder 12)
        - Asian Women at Work, 1994 (Box 146, Folder 13)
        - Bread for the World, 1990-1996 (Box 146, Folder 14)
        - Feliciano Carino, 1968-1970 (Box 146, Folder 15)
        - Center for Christian Response to Asian Issues (CCRAI), 1991-1992 (Box 146, Folder 16)
        - Christian Aid, 1991-1996 (Box 146, Folder 17)
        - Christian Center for Asian Studies, 1991-1994 (Box 146, Folder 18)
        - Christian Workers Fellowship (CWF), 1991-1995 (Box 146, Folder 19)
        - Committee for Asian Women (CAW), 1991-1994 (Box 146, Folder 20)
        - Samuel Coilpillai, 1983-1991 (Box 146, Folder 21)
        - Pepz Cunanan, 1985 (Box 146, Folder 22)
        - Harry Daniel, 1986-1991 (Box 146, Folder 23)
        - Alex Devasundaram, 1982-1990 (Box 146, Folder 24)
        - Documentation for Action Groups in Asia (DAGA) incl. reports, 1989-1993 (Box 146, Folder 25)
        - EACC Staff, 1968-1972 (Box 146, Folder 26)
        - Ediger Max, 1991-1995 (Box 146, Folder 27)
        - EZE, 1991-1995 (Box 146, Folder 28)
        - Federation of Asian Bishops' Conference (FABC), 1970-1976 (Box 146, Folder 29)
        - Correspondence re. Finance and Training Program, Hong Kong, 1968-1970 (Box 146, Folder 30)
        - Correspondence re. Finance and Training Program, India, 1966-1970 (Box 146, Folder 31)
        - Correspondence re. Finance and Training Program, Japan, 1969-1970 (Box 146, Folder 32)
        - Correspondence re. Finance and Training Program, Korea, 1967-1970 (Box 146, Folder 33)
        - Correspondence re. Finance and Training Program, Malaysia, 1969-1970 (Box 146, Folder 34)
        - Correspondence re. Finance and Training Program, Pakistan, 1968-1970 (Box 146, Folder 35)
        - Correspondence re. Finance and Training Program, Philippines, 1968-1970 (Box 146, Folder 36)
        - Correspondence re. Finance and Training Program, Sri Lanka, 1969-1970 (Box 146, Folder 37)
        - Correspondence re. Finance and Training Program, Taiwan, 1969-1970 (Box 146, Folder 38)
        - Correspondence re. Finance and Training Program, Thailand, 1969-1970 (Box 146, Folder 39)
        - Oscar Francisco, 1988-1993 (Box 146, Folder 40)
        - Ronald Fujiyoshi, 1968-1970, 1992 (Box 146, Folder 41)
        - John Garbutt, 1988-1990 (Box 146, Folder 42)
        - Correspondence, general, 1968-1970 (Box 146, Folder 43)
        - Correspondence, general, 1971-1974 (Box 146, Folder 44)
        - Correspondence, general, 1975 (Box 146, Folder 45)
        - Correspondence, general, 1975-1976 (Box 146, Folder 46)
        - Correspondence, general, 1980-1981 (Box 147, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence, general, 1982-1985 (Box 147, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence, general, 1987-1989 (Box 147, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence, general, 1991-1995, 1998 (Box 147, Folder 4)
        - Idara-E-Amn-O-Insaf, Committee for Justice and Peace, 1991-1995 (Box 147, Folder 5)
        - inter-unit, 1975-1976 (Box 147, Folder 6)
        - Isis Internacional incl. publication, 1992 (Box 147, Folder 7)
        - Victor Karunao, 1987-1989 (Box 147, Folder 8)
        - David Ken, 1979-1984 (Box 147, Folder 9)
        - Laymen abroad, 1967-1969 (Box 147, Folder 10)
        - Lutheran World Federation, 1990, 1995 (Box 147, Folder 11)
        - Kurata Masahiko, 1987-1991 (Box 147, Folder 12)
        - Koshy Mathew, 1971-1972 (Box 147, Folder 13)
        - Philip Mathew, 1983-1991 (Box 147, Folder 14)
        - Minority groups, 1967-1968 (Box 147, Folder 15)
        - Misereor, 1980-1986 (Box 147, Folder 16)
        - Mission to Filipino Migrant Workers, 1985-1992 (Box 147, Folder 17)
        - Mission agencies, 1968-1969 (Box 147, Folder 18)
        - Ron O'Grady, 1985-1990 (Box 147, Folder 19)
        - Sun Ai Park, 1982-1984 (Box 147, Folder 20)
        - People's Plan for the 21st Century (PP21), 1992 (Box 147, Folder 21)
        - People's Force, 1986-1989 (Box 147, Folder 22)
        - People's Organization for Participation, 1991-1995 (Box 147, Folder 23)
        - ProTEG, 1992-1993 (Box 147, Folder 24)
        - Bishop Poulose Mar Poulose, 1981-1986 (Box 147, Folder 25)
        - Correspondence re. Program Committee Meeting, 1994 (Box 147, Folder 26)
        - Ruth Prudente, 1985-1989 (Box 147, Folder 27)
        - Correspondence re. publications, 1976-1977, 1981 (Box 147, Folder 28)
        - Rev. Clyde O. Robinson, Fr., 1992-1993 (Box 147, Folder 29)
        - Oh Jae Shik, 1983-1993 (Box 147, Folder 30)
        - Rajan Singh, 1986-1993 (Box 147, Folder 31)
        - SOCO, 1973-1976 (Box 147, Folder 32)
        - Masao Takenaka, 1971-1972 (Box 147, Folder 33)
        - Theological Education Fund (TEF), 1973-1976 (Box 147, Folder 34)
        - Correspondence re. Theology in Action, 1972-1976 (Box 147, Folder 35)
        - Takami Toshihiro, 1983-1984 (Box 147, Folder 36)
        - Bakthan Tychicus, 1987-1991 (Box 147, Folder 37)
        - Correspondence re. URM Committee Meeting, 1991 (Box 147, Folder 38)
        - Correspondence re. URM Committee Meeting, 1993 (Box 147, Folder 39)
        - Correspondence re. URM Finances, 1976 (Box 147, Folder 40)
        - Correspondence re. URM Finance, URM budget, 1987 (Box 147, Folder 41)
        - Correspondence re. URM Finances, 1992-1996 (Box 147, Folder 42)
        - Henk Van Andel, 1972 (Box 147, Folder 43)
        - Vikas Adhyyan Kendra, 1981-1990 (Box 147, Folder 44)
        - Noel Villalba, 1988-1989 (Box 147, Folder 45)
        - World Student Federation for Asia (WSFA), 1971-1972 (Box 147, Folder 46)
        - WCC, 1986-1987 (Box 147, Folder 47)
        - WCC, 1988-1989 (Box 148, Folder 1)
        - WCC, 1990-1991 (Box 148, Folder 2)
        - WCC, 1992 (Box 148, Folder 3)
        - WCC (1 of 2), 1993-1995 (Box 148, Folder 4)
        - WCC (2 of 2), 1993-1995 (Box 148, Folder 5)
        - WCC/CCIA, 1989-1991 (Box 148, Folder 6)
        - WCC/CICARWS, 1991-1993 (Box 148, Folder 7)
        - WCC/Division of World Mission and Evangelism, 1971 (Box 148, Folder 8)
        - WCC/DICARWS, 1972-1973 (Box 148, Folder 9)
        - WCC/SWME, 1963-1972 (Box 148, Folder 10)
        - World Student Christian Federation (WSCF), 1983-1995 (Box 148, Folder 11)
        - YMCA, YWCA, 1991-1995 (Box 148, Folder 12)
        - Yong Dong Po Urban Industrial Mission, 1991-1995 (Box 148, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence by region/country
        - Africa, 1991-1994 (Box 148, Folder 14)
        - Australia, 1969-1976 (Box 148, Folder 15)
        - Australia, 1988-1990 (Box 148, Folder 16)
        - Australia, 1991-1995 (Box 148, Folder 17)
        - Bangladesh, 1983-1994 (Box 148, Folder 18)
        - Canada, 1992-1995 (Box 148, Folder 19)
        - Europe, 1974-1979 (Box 148, Folder 20)
        - Germany incl. Bread for the World, 1972-1976, 1993 (Box 148, Folder 21)
        - Hong Kong, 1968-1972 (Box 148, Folder 22)
        - Hong Kong, the Holy Carpenter Church Community Centre, 1972-1976 (Box 148, Folder 23)
        - Hong Kong, 1991-1995 (Box 148, Folder 24)
        - India, 1968-1976 (Box 148, Folder 25)
        - India (1 of 3), 1991-1995 (Box 148, Folder 26)
        - India (2 of 3), 1991-1995 (Box 148, Folder 27)
        - India (3 of 3), 1991-1995 (Box 148, Folder 28)
        - Indonesia, 1968-1976, 1981 (Box 149, Folder 1)
        - Indonesia (1 of 2), 1990-1995 (Box 149, Folder 2)
        - Indonesia (2 of 2), 1990-1995 (Box 149, Folder 3)
        - Japan, 1969-1976 (Box 149, Folder 4)
        - Japan, 1991-1995 (Box 149, Folder 5)
        - Japan, Korea Christian Church, 1991-1994 (Box 149, Folder 6)
        - Korea (1 of 2), 1969-1976 (Box 149, Folder 7)
        - Korea (2 of 2), 1969-1976 (Box 149, Folder 8)
        - Korea incl. Park San Jung paper "Christian Role for Democratization and Development in Asia", 1991-1995 (Box 149, Folder 9)
        - Latin America, 1990 (Box 149, Folder 10)
        - Malaysia, 1969-1976 (Box 149, Folder 11)
        - Malaysia, 1991-1995 (Box 149, Folder 12)
        - Malaysia, CCA-URM financial allocation, 1981-1993 (Box 149, Folder 13)
        - Myanmar, 1991-1995 (Box 149, Folder 14)
        - Middle East, 1975, 1989-1995 (Box 149, Folder 15)
        - Nepal, SPACE, 1991 (Box 149, Folder 16)
        - Netherlands, 1989-1995 (Box 149, Folder 17)
        - New Zealand, 1969-1976 (Box 149, Folder 18)
        - Pakistan, 1969-1973, 1994 (Box 149, Folder 19)
        - Papua New Guinea, 1991-1992 (Box 149, Folder 20)
        - Philippines (1 of 2), 1967-1976 (Box 149, Folder 21)
        - Philippines (2 of 2), 1967-1976 (Box 149, Folder 22)
        - Philippines, 1991-1995 (Box 149, Folder 23)
        - Singapore, 1967-1973, 1994 (Box 149, Folder 24)
        - Sri Lanka, 1969-1976 (Box 149, Folder 25)
        - Sri Lanka, 1990-1995 (Box 149, Folder 26)
        - Taiwan, 1967-1972 (Box 149, Folder 27)
        - Taiwan, 1989-1995 (Box 149, Folder 28)